{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Thermostat Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/39798/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39798,"taskName":"Thermostat - Repair or Reprogram","taskDescription":"Repair or Reprogram a Thermostat","xmTaskDescriptor":"Thermostat Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":241,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"thermostat regulator heat regulation warm","textMessagingName":"Repr Thermost","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes traditional fixed setting thermostats \u0026 modern programmable ones that allow the setting of different target temperatures for different days \u0026 hours. Typically handled by electricians, heating \u0026 cooling contractors \u0026 some appliance firms.","rolloverShortDesc":"Controls heating \u0026 cooling systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Reprogram a Thermostat.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Thermostat Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix a Thermostat","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Thermostat Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Thermostat - Repair or Reprogram","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Thermostat Project","urlName":"Thermostat-Repair-or-Reprogram","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Thermostat Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"thermostat,regulator,heat,regulation,warm, hvac","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":323,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39798/":{"taskOID":39798,"originalTaskOID":39798,"setID":323,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":3080,"questionDisplayText":"Thermostat type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of thermostat do you need repaired or replaced?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3736,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Manual thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Manual thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electronic, programmable model","answerDisplayText":"Electronic, programmable model","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3081,"questionDisplayText":"Heating System Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of heating system do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2683,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnace","answerDisplayText":"Furnace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1073,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Boiler radiator","answerDisplayText":"Boiler radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6063,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steam boiler radiator","answerDisplayText":"Steam boiler radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2156,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Electric baseboard - thermostat on unit","answerDisplayText":"Electric baseboard - thermostat on unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4995,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Radiant floor","answerDisplayText":"Radiant floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6954,"questionDisplayText":"Thermostat Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately how old is the thermostat needing repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10217,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1 year","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1 year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10218,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5 years","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10219,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10220,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10221,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":3080,"questionDisplayText":"Thermostat type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of thermostat do you need repaired or replaced?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3736,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Manual thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Manual thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electronic, programmable model","answerDisplayText":"Electronic, programmable model","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3736,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Manual thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Manual thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electronic, programmable model","answerDisplayText":"Electronic, programmable model","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3081,"questionDisplayText":"Heating System Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of heating system do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2683,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnace","answerDisplayText":"Furnace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1073,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Boiler radiator","answerDisplayText":"Boiler radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6063,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steam boiler radiator","answerDisplayText":"Steam boiler radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2156,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Electric baseboard - thermostat on unit","answerDisplayText":"Electric baseboard - thermostat on unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4995,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Radiant floor","answerDisplayText":"Radiant floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2683,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnace","answerDisplayText":"Furnace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1073,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Boiler radiator","answerDisplayText":"Boiler radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6063,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steam boiler radiator","answerDisplayText":"Steam boiler radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2156,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Electric baseboard - thermostat on unit","answerDisplayText":"Electric baseboard - thermostat on unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4995,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Radiant floor","answerDisplayText":"Radiant floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6954,"questionDisplayText":"Thermostat Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately how old is the thermostat needing repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10217,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1 year","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1 year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10218,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5 years","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10219,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10220,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10221,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10217,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1 year","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1 year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10218,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2 - 5 years","answerDisplayText":"2 - 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10219,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10220,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10221,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}